<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-02-16T11:31:37-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Eat the Frog</title><subtitle>Explore what inspires you.</subtitle><author><name>Mark Twain</name></author><entry><title type="html">Programmer Art</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/updates/games/snackrificial-chamber-programmer-art" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Programmer Art" /><published>2019-02-05T16:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-02-05T16:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/updates/games/snackrificial-chamber-programmer-art</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/updates/games/snackrificial-chamber-programmer-art">&lt;p&gt;I continue the remake by creating new models for the chicken, conveyor belt, and ritual circle as well as creating floor and wall tiles.  These models replace all of the placeholder art created in the previous episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a combination of MagicaVoxel, Photoshop, and remapped UVs to create the models I need for my game.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Mark Twain</name></author><summary type="html">I continue the remake by creating new models for the chicken, conveyor belt, and ritual circle as well as creating floor and wall tiles. These models replace all of the placeholder art created in the previous episode.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Core Mechanics</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/updates/games/snackrificial-chamber-core-mechanics" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Core Mechanics" /><published>2019-01-22T16:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-01-22T16:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/updates/games/snackrificial-chamber-core-mechanics</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/updates/games/snackrificial-chamber-core-mechanics">&lt;p&gt;I’ve begun the recreation of the game I made for Ludum Dare 43 (Sacrifices Must be Made).  I start by creating the required mechanics, conveyor belt movement and ritual circle sacrificing.  The cargo looks at the tile below it to determine where to go next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I follow the same process I use when creating a jam game and outline the ways in which I implemented features.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Mark Twain</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve begun the recreation of the game I made for Ludum Dare 43 (Sacrifices Must be Made). I start by creating the required mechanics, conveyor belt movement and ritual circle sacrificing. The cargo looks at the tile below it to determine where to go next.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Snackrificial Chamber</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/projects/games/snackrificial-chamber" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Snackrificial Chamber" /><published>2018-12-03T16:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-12-03T16:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/projects/games/snackrificial-chamber</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/projects/games/snackrificial-chamber">&lt;p&gt;Not sure how, but you managed to get yourself roped in with a cult led by the greatest snackers in history.  Please the Great Ones by preparing their favorite dish.  But be careful, if you don’t meet their requirements you’ll have to do it again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy snacking!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve been tasked with solving the logistics problems of a local cult and their snack factory.  It’s your job to fix the conveyor belts and prepare the chickens for consumption.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Mark Twain</name></author><summary type="html">Not sure how, but you managed to get yourself roped in with a cult led by the greatest snackers in history. Please the Great Ones by preparing their favorite dish. But be careful, if you don’t meet their requirements you’ll have to do it again. Happy snacking!</summary></entry></feed>